

REGINALD TAN

Aspiring Software Engineer

CONTACT ME

www.reginaldtan.com

reginald.140105@gmail.com

+65 80231103

github.com/klystrn

POSITIONS & ROLES

Head Secretary, EXCO Overflow 2023 - 2024

Workgroup Overflow 2022 - 2023

Service Leader School of Science & Technology 2019 - 2021

SKILLS & LANGUAGES

Python

C#

C++

ASP.NET Core

Databases & SQL

UI/UX Design

Data Structures

& Algorithms

ABOUT ME

Originally from the School of Science & Technology, Singapore, I specialised in Computing and led multiple service-learning events, including collaborations with Singapore Cancer Society & the National Youth Council.

I am studying Information Technology in Ngee Ann Polytechnic with 4 years of programming experience and interests in Full Stack Development and UI/UX Design. I am also the Head Secretary of Overflow, a Student-Initiated-Group which focuses on teaching current technologies and advanced programming.

EDUCATION

Ngee Ann Polytechnic Diploma in Information Technology

2022 - Present

In my time as an IT student in NP, I have been introduced to many skills & concepts, namely Object-Oriented Programming, ASP.NET Core, Data Structures & Algorithms, Databases & UI/UX design. I have also had the opportunity to develop my skills & interests programming languages such as Python, C#, C++ & JavaScript. Beyond my diploma, I have also helped organise events such as RED Camp & internal CCA events.

<u>School of Science & Technology, Singapore</u> 2018 - 2022 O'Levels with a Specialisation in Computing

Graduated from SST in 2021, I specialised in Computing, where I was introduced to concepts such as Computer Architecture, Networking, Artificial Intelligence & Machine Learning. I was also a Service Leader, who led multiple projects such as elderly interactions. Even after graduation, I have continued to be a part of the SST family, by giving talks to new cohorts & being a panelist for multiple open houses.

St. Stephen's School PSLE Certificate

2012 - 2017

As a primary school student, I had a keen interest for Mathematics & Science, participating in numerous Olympiads for both subjects. I was also part of the track & field & Taekwondo teams.



CONTACT ME

www.reginaldtan.com

reginald.140105@gmail.com

+65 80231103

github.com/klystrn

AWARDS

Ngee Ann Scholarship

2023

Director's List for Diploma in IT, Level 1

2022 & 2023

Second Most Outstanding Performance for Diploma in IT, Level 1

2022

Module Prizes in Computing Mathematics & Design Principles

2022

Bronze Award in DrCT 2021 (Design Thinking With Robotics & Computational Thinking International Competition)

2021

VALUES & QUALITIES

- Highly-motivated & keento-learn
- Open-minded
- · Adaptable & quick-learner
- · Detail-oriented
- Communicative & Collaborative

PROJECTS & EXPERIENCES

C#, OOP 2023

Hotel Guest Management System

For my final project in PRG2, I showcased my learning in OOP & C# by building a text-based program for a fictitious ICT hotel to manage hotel guests & rooms.

C++, Data Structures & Algorithms

2023

Food Ordering System

Using C++, I implemented data structures & algorithms with OOP to develop a text-based food ordering system for my final assignment in DSA.

HTML & CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap

2023

The Tea Shop - reginaldtan.com/TheTeaShop

In 2022, I had the opportunity to build a website for an online tea business using product renders & research my friends & I did. This was exciting as it was the first proper website I built from scratch.

Figma, MapBox, UI/UX Design

2023

AfterShip App Mockup Prototype

Using my learning from UX, I added my own personal twist to what I think a shipment tracking app can be, I created a mockup app prototype for Shipee, a rebranding of the popular app, Aftership.

Python, Pygame

2022

Tower Defence Game

Using Python, I built a text-based unit defence game (similar to Plants VS Zombies). In this project, I acquired experience in Python, PyGame, game design & logic.

Python, Data Structures

2021

locationX

As my capstone project in SST, my friends & I built locationX, a simple, text-based program to help our teacher plan matches for the National School Games, as he had been doing it manually.

Workshop Facilitator & Organiser

2022

Overflow Workshop on Vue

As part of the Overflow workgroup, I was given the opportunity to share about a tech topic of my interest. From there, I prepared materials & taught 2 workshops on Vue & DaisyUI to ICT students.

Planning Committee, Team-Leader

2018 & 2019

Overseas Learning Experiences to Brunei & Vietnam

In 2018 & 2019, I organised & led 2 overseas service-learning trips to Brunei & Vietnam, where we advocated about pollution, helped install solar panels in a commune, & taught local children.